[music]
Kar do
loot
Ajay ko
that Hello friends Yogendra Ram your
friend Sachcha Itihaas
you are very welcome to my channel Bhandar today and I would request
you in this video please watch this video till the
end and if you have not subscribed to my channel then
please
subscribe subscribe channel do
not forget to subscribe subscribe and if
you want both the things then I will subscribe in details if you have
problem and the
company is needed and the claim settlement has been done in a very good manner
that there is
no problem of any kind soon
subscribe and subscribe our Channel
subscribe Meghnad now school is his name and home let's
talk first of all
definitely subscribe to this
explanation first of all let's talk about generator
in ICC from 18 years to 10 subscribe so if you
subscribe here 18 then
they should subscribe
subscribe to the channel subscribe like and
subscribe talk channel then
appoint like and subscribe here
spread then money up to 50,000
is available at different times prizes
are written from 3 lakh to
4 lakh or you can participate  Tilak can subscribe, now let's
talk about subscribe video, you
can appoint a subscriber, let's
talk about romance and mysteries limit,
friends, there is no limit on time in the room, there is no
limit on subscription, do not forget to subscribe to the channel
and subscription is a different thing, if
you have not subscribed then I am
talking about subscription, this channel
is not even subscribed, if you
subscribe then you do
not get reception with the script,
friends, here you get the feature of recharge,
recharge means keep watching your hair appeal,
so the company Adidas releases time,
what was the reason for that, this provides employment,
friends, if Til is made of dates then you
get subscription, if you have not subscribed up to 5 lakhs
then please subscribe
and on any person, hence at this time you get any
subscription,
subscribe through recharge and subscribe and share,
subscribe to the channel,
this is the introduction of spring if the whole
family does the product, whereas
in this, this option is not available, Adidas is not
available, next let's talk about other features
like roadways  There is no limit to this in such a case,
you can use 300 rupees this year. If we talk about it, then
subscribe and subscribe
[music]
appointment, appointment,
sexual issues, joint replacement,
all these diseases will be the second news in ICC
this year. This is also a coincidence. If we
talk about net comment, then both are
very important for 19 days. Such channel has acidity
and if we talk about partner, then
subscribe to whichever work is difficult,
it is generally very good and
both accused. Apart from this, friends, do
not forget to subscribe and subscribe to the channel and
subscribe and subscribe to that, you
get Hindi peace inside the mosque, friends and family get total,
whatever you want, you can take it in both options.
Apart from this, you and special
went in it. Delivery sponge, yes friends,
delivery in such quantity is not agreed
that in Star's policy, Delivery
Express news is that 10 and 10 crore jobs have been
found, after that we will need to stop,
so if you reach the premiere in Daily Express, if we
talk about it, then both are for both.  If you subscribe inside
then both are very disgusting subscirbe
people can talk from here we do
animal light we provide all over India plus I
hope you have
understood the video any kind of
problems you can call me hello
Yogesh Tanwar